{
    "id": "a093e638453c448e854b596e75a27609",
    "title": "Few, A Few, Little, A Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………… apprehensive about his reaction.",
            "description": "A little has a positive meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84204f0360524b7a88675e08573aac25"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………………. friends that I can trust.",
            "description": "Use few with plural nouns and little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd8928531aee413caea98d06656385f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ……………………… concerned about his health.",
            "description": "Few is used with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "a little",
                "few",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f61acd7426144906ab364dc9d398a0a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ……………………….. interest in politics.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns and few with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "986360359f6743738a4d24bb3468ddc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "Either few or a few is possible here with slightly different meanings. Few politicians means hardly any politicians a few politicians means a small number of politicians. ",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little",
                "A few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5b175df9bde477cb888f08b058b5254"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are only …………………………. copies left.",
            "description": "Write a few after limiting words like only. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1214caea082149188e6c607d3c7d7251"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to ask ………………………… questions.",
            "description": "A few means a small number. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c20089137592433bb3c43d8c360d3310"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got …………………………. water if you are thirsty.",
            "description": "A little indicates a small amount. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ba96be53a6d4462af7901c5fb3d8404"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………… annoyed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96534c34bf9c4dcf93751a7e668b30e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only ……………………….. students in this class will pass the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1ba41408925a4983b86d4e985b2cfce0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know I have very ……………………….. options.",
            "description": "Use few after very.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8330f12251b841518835b8f42a0c7338"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have very ………………………. money.",
            "description": "Use little after very. Use little with uncountable things like money. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4badb218afca43b89d7b16312898f562"
        }
    ]
}